{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What is Everest&#039;s favorite food in the Nickelodeon/Nick Jr. series &quot;PAW Patrol&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Liver",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Chicken",
        "Steak",
        "Caribou"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the 1993 Disney animated series &quot;Bonkers&quot;, what is the name of Bonker&#039;s second partner?",
      "correct_answer": "Miranda Wright",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Dick Tracy",
        "Eddie Valiant",
        "Dr. Ludwig von Drake"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of the following did not feature in the cartoon &#039;Wacky Races&#039;?",
      "correct_answer": "The Dragon Wagon",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "The Bouldermobile",
        "The Crimson Haybailer",
        "The Compact Pussycat"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What is the relationship between Rick and Morty in the show &quot;Rick and Morty&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "Grandfather and Grandson",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Father and Son",
        "Best Friends",
        "Crimefighting Partners"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "What was the first Disney movie to use CGI?",
      "correct_answer": "The Black Cauldron",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Tron",
        "Toy Story",
        "Fantasia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Who created the Cartoon Network series &quot;Regular Show&quot;?",
      "correct_answer": "J. G. Quintel",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ben Bocquelet",
        "Pendleton Ward",
        "Rebecca Sugar"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In the show &quot;Steven Universe&quot;, who are the main two employees of The Big Donut?",
      "correct_answer": "Sadie and Lars",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Steven and James",
        "Erik and Julie",
        "Bob and May"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In South Park, what is Stan&#039;s surname?",
      "correct_answer": "Marsh",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Stotch",
        "Broflovski",
        "Tweak"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "In &quot;Avatar: The Last Airbender&quot;, which element does Aang begin to learn after being defrosted?",
      "correct_answer": "Water",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Air",
        "Earth",
        "Fire"
      ]
    },
    {
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "category": "Entertainment: Cartoon &amp; Animations",
      "question": "Which of these is NOT a Disney cartoon character?",
      "correct_answer": "Daffy Duck",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Donald Duck",
        "Daisy Duck",
        "Scrooge McDuck"
      ]
    }
  ]
}